Katharine Kuh
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1908-1994, Series 2:; (Boxes 1-5, 13-14, OV 15; 4.0 linear feet)
  - Oversize Birthday Card with Drawing by Juliet Kepes, Jul 15, 1975 (Box OV 15)
- Personal Business Records, 1941-1989, Series 3:; (Box 5; 19 folders)
  Personal business records include a list of artwork, Olga Woolf's will, inventories of Kuh's personal art collection, miscellaneous contracts and deeds of gift, receipts for sales of artwork, files concerning business-related travel, and miscellaneous receipts.
  - List of artwork Donated to the Art Institute of Chicago by Olga Woolf, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Will of Olga Woolf, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Partial Inventory of Katharine Kuh's Personal Art Collection, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Inventory of Katharine Kuh's Personal Art Collection, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Appraisal of Katharine Kuh's Art Property, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Book Contracts, 1951-1969 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Contracts, 1968-1984, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Copies of Archives of American Art Deeds of Gift, 1971-1989 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Receipts for the Sale of artwork, 1968-1976, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 26-27)
  - File Concerning Travel to Japan for The Saturday Review, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - File Concerning Grant-Funded Travel to Survey artwork in India for the Smithsonian Institution, 1979-1980, (6 folders) (Box 5, Folder 29-34)
  - Miscellaneous Travel Receipts, 1977-1979, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous Business Records, 1971, undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Artwork, 1931-1986, Series 4:; (Boxes 5, 13-14, OVs 15-23; 1.7 linear feet)
  Artwork consists of drawings, watercolors, paintings, and prints by various artists including Josef Albers, Angelica Archipenko, Saradell Ard, Lee Atwood, Serge Chermayeff, Julio De Diego, William Fett, Leon Golub, David Hare, Anne Humenfeld, Boris Margo, Carlos Mérida, Wallace Putnam, Jesse Reichek, Jeff Schlanger, Shelby Shackelford, Hedda Sterne, Hugo Weber, Cady Wells, Bill Westheimer, Emerson Woelffer, and Robert Jay Wolff. There are also drawings by Eskimo children and a watercolor set, Technics and Creativity, designed and autographed by Jasper Johns for the Museum of Modern Art, 1970.
  - Drawings by Unidentified Artists, 1956-1974, undated, (2 folders; see also Box 13) (Box 5, Folder 37-38)
  - Watercolor Painting and Prints by Unidentified Artists, undated, (see also Box 13 and OV 15) (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Collages, Trompe L'Oeil Painting, and Mail Art by Unidentified Artists, 1975-1985, undated, (see also Boxes 13, 14) (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Plastic Book Containing Photographs of Desert Sand Patterns by an Unidentified Artist, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Artwork by Joseph Albers, 1960, undated, (see also Box 14) (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Artwork by Angelica Archipenko, Saradell Art, and Elise Asher, 1984, undated, (see also Box 13 and OV 19) (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Artwork by Lee Atwood, 1931-1941, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 44-45)
  - Artwork by Rainey Bennett, Fred Berman, and Helen Binkley, 1951-1980, (see also OV 2) (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Artwork by Robert Bissière, M. Block, Copeland Burg, and Victor Candell, 1958-1971, undated, (see also Box 13) (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Artwork by Serge Chermayeff, 1963-1984, undated, (see also Box 13 and OV 16) (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Artwork by Al Copley, Worden Day, Julio De Diego, and Lois Dodd, 1945-1969, undated, (see also Box 13) (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Artwork by William Fett, Mary Frank, and Giroux, 1952-1970, undated, (see also OV 19) (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Artwork by Marshall Glasier, 1940-1950 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Artwork by Leon Golub, Joseph Goto, and David Hare, 1966-1972, undated (see also OVs 20-22) (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Artwork by Anne Humenfeld, Jasper Johns, and Joan Kahn, 1970-1984, undated, (see also Box 14 and OV 23) (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Artwork by Olivia Kahn, Gyorgy and Juliet Kepes, Michael Leonard, and David Marcowitz, 1965-1986, undated, (see also Box 13 and OV 17) (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Artwork by Boris Margo, undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Artwork by Martyl and Mendez, 1951, undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Artwork by Carlos Mérida, 1938, undated (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Artwork by Tino Nivola, Harold Paris, Wallace Putnam, and Jesse Reichek, 1979, undated, (see also Box 13) (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Artwork by Felix Ruvolo, 1939, undated (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Artwork by Jeff Schlanger, Charles Seliger, and Shelby Shackelford, 1963-1985, (see also Box 13, OVs 18, 23) (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Artwork by Hedda Sterne, 1949-1972, undated, (see also Box 13 and OV 18) (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Artwork by Lenore Tawney, J. Urbain, A. Walsh, and BurtonWasserman, 1968-1981 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Artwork by Hugo Weber and Cady Wells, undated, (see also OV 19) (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Artwork by Bill Westheimer, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Artwork by Emerson Woelffer, Robert J. Wolff, and Jan Yoors, 1966-1977 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Artwork by Eskimo Children, 1960-1969 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Oversize Portrait Caricature Lithograph of Katharine Kuh by Unidentified Artist, undated (Box 13 (sol))
  - Oversize Portrait Drawing of Katharine Kuh by Unidentified Artist, probably 1956 (Box 13 (sol))
  - Oversize Collage Formed with Masking Tape by Unidentified Artist, 1975 (Box 13 (sol))
  - Oversize Drawing by Angelica Archipenko, undated (Box 13 (sol))
  - Oversize Color Lithograph by Roger Bissière, 1958 (Box 13 (sol))
  - Oversize Woodcut "Spring" by Victor Candell, undated (Box 13 (sol))
  - Oversize Drawing for "Painting A" by Serge Chermayeff, 1963 (Box 13 (sol))
  - Oversize Silkscreen "Now Flowing" by Worden Day, undated (Box 13 (sol))
  - Oversize Silkscreen by Olivia Kahn, 1965 (Box 13 (sol))
  - Oversize Etching by Gyorgy and Juliet Kepes, undated (Box 13 (sol))
  - Oversize Lithograph One Feather - Miracle Enough by Wallace Putnam, undated (Box 13 (sol))
  - Oversize Drawing The Cove, Wellfleet by Shelby Shackelford, 1985 (Box 13 (sol))
  - Oversize Painting on Cloth by Hedda Sterne, undated (Box 13 (sol))
  - Three Oversize Drawings by Hedda Sterne, 1949-1972 (Box 13 (sol))
  - Oversize Form Made with Molded Paper by Unidentified Artist, undated (Box 14)
  - Trompe L'Oeil Painting on a Paper Plate by Margy, undated (Box 14)
  - Oversize Abstract Incised Pattern Mounted on Wood by Josef Albers, 1960 (Box 14)
  - White Plastic Box Technics and Creativity Containing a Blank "Target 1970," a Brush and Watercolor Paint Blocks, signed by Jasper Johns for the Museum of Modern Art, 1970 (Box 14)
  - Oversize Portrait Painting of Katharine Kuh by Unidentified Artist, undated (Box OV 15)
  - Oversize Etching "Sea Wall" by Fred Berman, 1963 (Box OV 16)
  - Oversize Collage/Painting "Red Vase #1" by Serge Chermayeff, 1965 (Box OV 16)
  - Oversize Silkscreen by Michael Leonard, undated (Box OV 17)
  - Oversize Photograph Paperback Books by David Marcowitz, 1986 (Box OV 17)
  - Oversize Pencil and Watercolor Sketch by Jeff Schlanger, 1981 (Box OV 18)
  - Oversize Etching Cove by Jeff Schlanger, 1982 (Box OV 18)
  - Oversize Drawing by Hedda Sterne, 1970 (Box OV 18)
  - Oversize Silkscreen "Exuberant Colors" by Saradell Ard, 1984 (Box OV 19)
  - Oversize Gouache Painting "Plants Forming" by William Fett, 1961 (Box OV 19)
  - Oversize Drawing by Hugo Weber, undated (Box OV 19)
  - Oversize Portfolio of Lithographs by David Hare, 1972 (Box OV 20)
  - Oversize Portfolio of Lithographs by David Hare, 1972 (Box OV 21)
  - Oversize Portfolio of Lithographs by David Hare, 1972 (Box OV 22)
  - Oversize Etching by Anne Humenfeld, 1984 (Box OV 23)
  - Oversize Etching Peacework by Jeff Schlanger, 1983 (Box OV 23)
- Notes and Writings, 1914-1994, Series 5:; (Boxes 5-7; 1.7 linear feet)
  Notes and writings include engagement calendars containing brief daily entries, travel journals for Germany, a guest book for the Kuh Memorial gathering, miscellaneous notes and writings, many for lectures, by Kuh concerning art history topics and business-related travel. Of interest are minutes/notes from meetings for art festivals, conferences, and the "Conversations with Artists Program (1961). There are also writings about Kuh and art-related topics by others including Josef Albers, Len Lye, and Daniel Catton Rich. Additional published printed articles and a book of poetry are filed with Printed Materials.
  - Engagement Calendars, 1964-1970, undated (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Engagement Calendars, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Engagement Calendars, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Engagement Calendars, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Engagement Calendars, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Engagement Calendars, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Engagement Calendars, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Engagement Calendars, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Engagement Calendars, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Engagement Calendars, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Engagement Calendars, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Engagement Calendars, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Engagement Calendars, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Engagement Calendars, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Travel Journals for Germany, 1954, (4 folders) (Box 6, Folder 4-7)
  - Draft for a Projected Book, undated, (4 folders) (Box 6, Folder 8-11)
  - Guestbook for Kuh Memorial Gathering, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Notebook, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Notes Concerning artwork, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Poems by Katharine Kuh for her Friends, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Typescript of Speech "Art as Communicator," Delivered by Kuh at Auburn University, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Typescript by Kuh for Exhibition "Both Sides of American Art," undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Typescript by Kuh: "How Real is Realism?," undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Typescript by Kuh for Cezanne Exhibition, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Manuscript by Kuh Concerning Frank Lloyd, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Typescript by Kuh Concerning the Acquisition of Work by Picabia, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Typescript by Kuh: "Caravaggio," undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Typescript by Kuh: "Workshop in Looking," undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Typescript by Kuh as a Child: "The Storm," 1914 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Typescript by Kuh: "Explaining Art Visually," 1940 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Typescript by Kuh: "Brief Report on Art Collections and Ruins Visited by Katharine Kuh During the Summer of 1945," 1945 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Typescript by Kuh: "Footnotes from a Latin American Page," 1945 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Typescript by Kuh: "Tropical and Strategic Agriculture in Central America," 1945 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Typescript by Kuh: "The U.S. in Middle America," 1945 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Typescript by Kuh: "A Central American Union," 1945 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Typescript by Kuh: "Tourism in Central America," 1945 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Typescript by Kuh: "Inflation in Guatemala," 1945 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Typescript by Kuh: "A National Agricultural School in Guatemala," 1945 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Typescript by Kuh: "Germans in Guatemala," 1945 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Typescript by Kuh: "Guatemalan Ghosts of Ubico," 1945 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Typescript by Kuh: "Mining in Honduras," 1945 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Typescript by Kuh: "Unrest in El Salvador," 1945 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Report by Kuh: "Preservation of Indian Art in Southeastern Alaska," 1946 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Report by Kuh on the Trip Through the Western Section of the United States, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Notes by Kuh Concerning Art Acquisitions for the First National Bank of Chicago, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Notes and Typescripts by Kuh for Horizon Magazine, 1959, (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 41-42)
  - Notes and Typescripts by Kuh Concerning a Recording Project, 1961, (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 43-44)
  - Typescript by Kuh Concerning a Visit to the U.S.S.R., 1963 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Notes by Kuh on Cosmo Campoli, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Notes by Kuh Concerning the Preservation of Monuments in Israel, 1967-1975 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Notes and Typescript by Kuh for a Film Series on Masters of Modern Art, 1979-1987, (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 48-49)
  - Notes and Typescript by Kuh Concerning Lenore Tawney, 1983, (3 folders) (Box 6, Folder 50-52)
  - Notes by Kuh for Lectures at the Cooper Union, 1983-1984, (4 folders) (Box 6, Folder 53-56)
  - Notes by Kuh for Lecture at the Anchorage Museum, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Typescript by Kuh: "Joe Shapiro: An Appreciation," 1984 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Notes by Kuh on Stuart Davis, 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Notes by Kuh for Report on Vassar College Art Gallery, 1984-1990, (5 folders) (Box 6, Folder 60-64)
  - Manuscript by Kuh Concerning Gertrude Abercrombie, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Notes by Kuh on Fernand Léger, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Miscellaneous Notes and Writings by Kuh, 1958-1985, undated, (9 folders) (Box 6, Folder 67-75)
  - Typescript by Unidentified Author Concerning Katharine Kuh, undated (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Typescript by Unidentified Author: "A Day with Kay," undated (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Typescript by Unidentified Author: "Shiny Gilt Frame is Gone," undated (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Typescript by Unidentified Author: "Abstract Expressionism (A Re-Evaluation)," undated (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Typescript by Unidentified Author: "M.O.M.A. as Renovated - A Spiritual Lift!," undated (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Typescript by Pat Dickinson: "Edwin Dickinson," undated (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Typescript by Len Lye: "Roundhead I," undated (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Typescript by Wallace Putnam: "Galileo to Warhol---?," undated, (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Typescript by Daniel Catton Rich: "Arthur Jerome Eddy - Portrait of a Collector," 1931 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Reports on the Fourth Annual San Francisco Art Festival, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Writings by Josef Albers, 1958-1961, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript by Len Despres: "Katharine Kuh's Farewell Address," 1959 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Minutes of the Fourth "Conversations with Artists" Program, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Excerpt from Article by Len Lye: "Why Art is Great and Ideology Isn't," 1962 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Typescript by Len Lye: "Keeping Up with the Muses," 1964 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Typescript by Jean Pierre Burgart: "Jean Hélion," 1966 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Minutes from the Conference on Southeast Alaska Native Artifacts and Monuments, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Poems to Katharine Kuh by Miscellaneous Authors, 1976-1982, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Poems by Daniel Catton Rich, 1976, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Eulogies for Daniel Catton Rich by Miscellaneous Authors, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Typescript by Unidentified Author Concerning Edward Corbett, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Master's Thesis by Janet Landay: "The (Surrealist) State vs. David Hare," 1980 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Typescript about Katharine Kuh by Unidentified Author, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Typescript by Stanley Kunitz: "Jack Tworkov," 1982 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Typescript by Susan J. Barnes Concerning Mark Rothko and the De Menil Chapel, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Typescript by Michael Lipton: "Eulogy for Seymour Lipton," 1986 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Annual Report from the Allen Memorial Art Museum, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Typescript by Avis Berman for a Book Chapter "The Katharine Kuh Gallery: An Informal Portrait," 1988, (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 22-23)
  - Notes by Avis Berman for Lecture "The Katharine Kuh Gallery: An Informal Portrait," 1988 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Typescript by Susan F. Rossen: "Primer for Seeing: The Gallery of Art Interpretation," 1990 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Report by McKinsey & Company, Inc. for the Art Institute of Chigago: "Museum Strategic Direction for the 1990s," 1990 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Writings, 1962-1965, undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Scrapbooks, 1935-1953, Series 6:; (Box 7; 8 folders)
  Six scrapbooks contain clippings that document the height of Kuh's career as a gallery director and museum curator. Scrapbook 6 contains clippings about Fernand Léger, the subject of a retrospective exhibition at the Art Institute of Chicago in 1953.
  - Scrapbook 1, 1935-1940 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Scrapbook 2, 1937-1939 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Scrapbook 3, 1939-1941 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Scrapbook 4, 1942-1946 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Scrapbook 5, 1950, (3 folders) (Box 7, Folder 32-34)
  - Scrapbook 6, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Printed Material, 1916-1922, Series 7:; (Boxes 7-10, 13, OV 22; 3.0 linear feet)
  Printed material includes clippings about Kuh, clippings of Kuh's articles for The Saturday Review, exhibition announcements and catalogs for miscellaneous artists, calendars of events, programs, brochures for art schools, brochures for seminars and lectures, and brochures for the purchase of books and artwork including one for lithographs by Robert Rauschenberg. There are also miscellaneous booklets, books including Poems by Kuh as a child, and reproductions of artwork. Some of the exhibition catalogs are from the Katharine Kuh Gallery, others contain essays written by Kuh, and they represent artists including Jean Arp, Marc Chagall, Jean Dubuffet, Marcel Duchamp, Stanley William Hayter, Hans Hofmann, Paul Klee, Franz Kline, Le Corbusier, Ludwig Mies van der Rohe, LeRoy Neiman, and Pablo Picasso.
  - Clippings, undated, (3 folders) (Box 7, Folder 36-38)
  - Clippings, 1928-1939 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Clippings, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Clippings, 1942-1944 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Clippings, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Clippings, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Clippings, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Clippings, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Clippings, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Clippings, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Clippings, 1951, (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 48-49)
  - Clippings, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Clippings, 1953, (4 folders) (Box 7, Folder 51-54)
  - Clippings, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Clippings, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Clippings, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Clippings, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Clippings, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Clippings, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Clippings, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Clippings, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Clippings, 1962, (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 63-64)
  - Clippings, 1963, (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 65-66)
  - Clippings, 1964, (3 folders) (Box 7, Folder 67-69)
  - Clippings, 1965, (4 folders) (Box 7, Folder 70-73)
  - Clippings, 1966, (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 74-75)
  - Clippings, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Clippings, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Clippings, 1969, (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
  - Clippings, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1971, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
  - Clippings, 1972, (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 7-9)
  - Clippings, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, 1977, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 14-15)
  - Clippings, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Clippings, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Clippings, 1980, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 18-19)
  - Clippings, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Clippings, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Clippings, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Clippings, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Clippings, 1987, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 25-26)
  - Clippings, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Clippings, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Clippings, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Clippings, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Kuh's Articles for The Saturday Review, undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Kuh's Articles for The Saturday Review, 1952-1959 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Kuh's Articles for The Saturday Review, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Kuh's Articles for The Saturday Review, 1961, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 34-35)
  - Kuh's Articles for The Saturday Review, 1962, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 36-37)
  - Kuh's Articles for The Saturday Review, 1963, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 38-39)
  - Kuh's Articles for The Saturday Review, 1964, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 40-41)
  - Kuh's Articles for The Saturday Review, 1965, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 42-43)
  - Kuh's Articles for The Saturday Review, 1966, (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 44-46)
  - Kuh's Articles for The Saturday Review, 1967, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 47-48)
  - Kuh's Articles for The Saturday Review, 1968, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 49-50)
  - Kuh's Articles for The Saturday Review, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Kuh's Articles for The Saturday Review, 1970, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 52-53)
  - Kuh's Articles for The Saturday Review, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Kuh's Articles for The Saturday Review/World, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Kuh's Articles for The Saturday Review/World, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Kuh's Articles for The Saturday Review/World, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Kuh's Articles for The Saturday Review/World, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Kuh's Articles for The Saturday Review/World, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Kuh's Articles for The Saturday Review/World, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, undated, (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 61-63)
    - Katharine Kuh Gallery, undated, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 64-65)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1934-1937 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1948, (3 folders) (Box 8, Folder 70-72)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1949, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 73-74)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1953, (4 folders) (Box 8, Folder 78-81)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1954, (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 82-83)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1955, (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1956, (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1958, (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 6-7)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1960, (see also OV 22) (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1962, (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 11-12)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1963, (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 13-14)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1964, (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 15-16)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1965, (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 17-18)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1966, (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 19-20)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1967, (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 21-22)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1970, (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 25-26)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1972, (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 28-29)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1975, (3 folders) (Box 9, Folder 32-34)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1977, (see also OV 22) (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1978, (3 folders) (Box 9, Folder 37-39)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1979, (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 40-41)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1982, (4 folders) (Box 9, Folder 44-47)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1983, (3 folders) (Box 9, Folder 48-50)
    - Miscellaneous Artists, 1984, (2 folders) (Box 9, Folder 51-52)